# ZAIN ALABDEEN KHARTABIL

Web Developer



# **ABOUT ME**

Creative and forward-thinking with history building cutting edge websites and applications with challenging demands and visions. with 4+ years of experience in developing and designing web applications and managing databases.

🔀 zainkhartabel1995@gmail.com

+40 791 434 445

linkedin.com/in/zain-alabdeenkhartabil-662019192

https://zainkhartabel.github.io/

# **LANGUAGES**

Romanian

## **EDUCATION**

## **BSc in Information Technology Engineering (2021)**

**Damascus University** 

**Software & Information Systems Engineering** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Sham Innovation SRL**

Full Stack Web Developer 11/2020 - 12/2021 Bucharest, Romania

C#, .Net Core & .Net 5
MSSQL Server & Entity Framework
Blazor
HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript , Bootstrap & Jquery

#### **Orbits Ideal Solutions**

Full Stack Web Developer 10/2019 - 10/2020 Damascus, Syria

C#, .Net Framework & .Net Core MSSQL Server ,MySQL & Entity Framework HTML, CSS, Javascript , Bootstrap & Jquery

### **MY SKILLS**







HTML

CSS

Java Scrip







**COURSES** 

BIG DATA ANALYTICS: OPPORTUNITIES, CHALLENGES, AND THE FUTURE (3/2021)
Griffith University

# **VOLUNTEERING**

#### IT Support (8/2015 - 12/2018)

**Damascus University** 

Maintenance of laboratories in the faculty of Information Technology Engineering

#### **HOBBIES**









Reading

Football

Swimming

Music